<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Joel Aguilozi</title>
    <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Joel Aguilozi</description>
    <image>
      <title>Joel Aguilozi</title>
      <url>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/images/author_quad.png</url>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/images/author_quad.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>2021 - 2024 Joel Aguilozi. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Helpfex</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/projects/helpfex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/projects/helpfex/</guid>
      <description>It was born with the idea of being a serious and different social network, and it is!.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiempo Gamer</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/projects/tiempo-gamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/projects/tiempo-gamer/</guid>
      <description>Tiempo Gamer Media website. Editor Chief. Gaming and technology reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/cuentos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/cuentos/</guid>
      <description>Some stories by Joel Aguilozzi available to read online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four words</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/01/</guid>
      <description>Four words © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
On the surface of the sea, four words sailed aimlessly; their names: Wind, Fire, Rock and Water. Agua didn&amp;rsquo;t mind sailing aimlessly, in fact, he loved it! On the other hand, Fire, despite being contained in a bottle and lit on a small piece of paper, was agonizing with fear due to the proximity of Water; and even when his pain was atrocious, Wind tried to save him as best he could every time the poor thing seemed to be extinguished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life&#39;s little things</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/07/</guid>
      <description>Life&amp;rsquo;s little things © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
Tell the story&amp;hellip; no, it started badly, like it did a few years ago when I started writing, it definitely started badly, badly, like Edward Venit the day his life changed forever.
One day, Edward went to sleep, upset at his lack of luck; So much so that he earned the nickname &amp;ldquo;yeta Venit&amp;rdquo;. That day Edward invoked whoever would listen to him from beyond, from another galaxy, or who knows where, to free him from his bad luck&amp;hellip;And he was heard; Edward transformed himself, just as Gregorio Samsa did, into an insect; the good luck insect!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love is not a crime</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/05/</guid>
      <description>Love is not a crime © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
I woke up to the gray light of dawn; I had spent a quiet, dreamless night, and I felt like a new man. However, my concerns remained the same as always, the hours of rest did not change anything. I looked out the window.
Iván, in his underwear, shook the carpet in the middle of the park.
He greeted me cordially like every day; I asked him why he shook the carpet so hard, &amp;ldquo;I washed it yesterday&amp;rdquo; I told him; I smiled and thought &amp;ldquo;his obsession hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed since I met him, he always wants to have everything in order, maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what sparked part of my love for him&amp;rdquo;, I still remember the day when I told my father that I had fallen in love&amp;hellip; And How can I not remember him, if that was the last day I spent in my house, the last day he spoke to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark&#39;s Mission</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/06/</guid>
      <description>Mark&amp;rsquo;s Mission © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
Mark bought his first house with the money he saved from his job on cruise ships. He spoke fluently Spanish, German, French and even a little Russian and of course English, his native language.
He had been away from England for three months and the month of November was already entering. They had crossed the Atlantic to Barbados and I was looking forward to return to your new home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remind yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/10/</guid>
      <description>Remind yourself © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
What is immortality? And why do many desire it so fervently? I sat down and I would have liked to have a cup of tea, because I need some time to tell you my story, they told me It tastes &amp;ldquo;very delicious&amp;rdquo; it&amp;rsquo;s a shame but I never could nor will I be able to taste it. Have you ever imagined a world without feelings?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver for Rest</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/09/</guid>
      <description>Silver for Rest © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
Helsinki, 1920. Jukka and Kalevi were looking for the town doctor, a man named Eikki. The work had to be quick and easy. The pay was good.
With the rifle with silver bullets behind them, they arrived at the doctor&amp;rsquo;s house when the sun was just rising. They knocked on the door without caring if the man was still sleeping. He opened it, and upon seeing them, he suspected who they were (in small towns there are things that are impossible to hide).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beginning</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/03/</guid>
      <description>The beginning © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
For a while I decide to leave everything as it is; I need to assimilate these changes. I don&amp;rsquo;t move, I just wait for the moment!&amp;hellip; Wait a minute&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to expect! I am recovering my original form. Something creaks and creaks again. From time to time I shudder. There is a part of me that seems to cry; However, I feel fine, although a little dazed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The essential is invisible to the eyes</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/08/</guid>
      <description>The essential is invisible to the eyes © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
Outside, the sun was shining brightly, for everyone except Adrian.
His case was extremely rare; He was almost blind during the day, but not at night. And he wasn&amp;rsquo;t albino.
Until now, no other person in the world was known to suffer from this very rare disease, so since they noticed this anomaly when he was just a child, they nicknamed him “the dark child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Consolation</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/02/</guid>
      <description>The Last Consolation © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
I was running in a forest. He didn&amp;rsquo;t distinguish colors. Everything looked black and white. Someone was chasing me. I just ran, ran, ran.
I felt terror, and I told myself; “this is my end.” I closed the eyes. Wait. Nothing was happening, so I decided to open them. That being extended his hand in a friendly manner and said: join me and do justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pharox Paradox</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/04/</guid>
      <description>The Pharox Paradox © Joel Aguilozi, 2020
Sometimes when we are not satisfied with our lives, with what wedo, we mistakenly wish for changes that did not occur, and weask ourselves, What if I had done this? What would my life belike? If I had finished university? Or would I have mademore money? Paradoxes exist, many of us ignore them,and for some they can become a more than disastrous reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Thousand Days and One Night</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/5000-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/5000-d/</guid>
      <description>ISBN	1370650345, 9781370650347</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Kabbalah</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/project-kabbalah/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/books/project-kabbalah/</guid>
      <description>ISBN	9781386314745</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m Joel Aguilozi, a Science Fiction writer eager to expand my horizons and venture into the world of production and artistic direction. As a passionate art enthusiast, I have worked as a chronicler and photographer at music concerts, and I am very dedicated to video games as a fan, gamer, tester, and analyst.
I have always enjoyed creating things, and to my writing production, I add experiences in programming and 3D design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Library</title>
      <link>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.joelaguilozi.com.ar/library/</guid>
      <description>Reading Software Engineering at Google: Lessons Learned from Programming Over Time by Titus Winters, Tom Manshreck, Hyrum Wright The Phoenix Project: A Novel about IT, DevOps, and Helping Your Business Win by Gene Kim, Kevin Behr, George Spafford Mastering Vim Quickly: From WTF to OMG in no time by Jovica Ilic Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software by Erich Gamma, Richard Helm, Ralph Johnson, John Vlissides La semana laboral de 4 horas by Timothy Ferriss Read The Go Programming Language by Alan A.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
